hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jeremy
Krakowski and I help coaches mentors
speakers and trainers make so much money
in their business that they can impact
more people with the cash flow that
comes in and listen I'm the guy that
helps you get rich and wealthy as a
coach and that's what we're going to be
talking about is why making a ton of
money is a good thing and shifting your
perspective out of a poverty mindset
I did a couple of events this week and I
was shocked by the feedback that I got
from quite a few people that they
thought the concept of making a ton of
money was bad and evil and not a good
thing for them and and to be honest if
that's you if you think about that I
hope that maybe you might be encouraged
to listen to something from a different
perspective
uh but honestly I have a feeling that
there's sort of a dividing line in our
culture between people between uh
capitalism around how can we make as
much money as possible and then use that
money to grow reach more people create
better things impact people better as
well or the side of let's make no money
but let's just make really good content
and let's hope that the content drives
itself and goes viral
and so what I'm finding is is that in my
audience in my Niche that there's a
dividing line in that and and that the
people that actually work with me
understand that making money is a very
important part of it
and I kind of avoided this for a little
while
um mainly because I didn't want to
offend people and and I was really like
trying to honor everybody and stuff like
that now I'm I'm at the point where I'm
just like if you don't want to make a
ton of money
or you're not at least willing to
start thinking in that direction of
making a ton of money you're probably
not going to resonate with me at all
and so let's talk about why it's a good
thing to make a ton of money
is I believe that it allows you to have
far more impact I can hire people very
easily when I'm making a half a million
dollars a year plus in my business I can
run advertising campaigns without
worrying about how we're going to pay
this budget you know we just ran a ten
thousand dollar ad campaign and by the
way it might not produce the results I
was hoping for it I took a risk with the
offer in the copy I I tested out
something that I wasn't sure how it was
going to convert and you know it so far
isn't converting how I thought but
because we have cash flow in our
business it's not gonna bankrupt us
because of it I'm just gonna go do
another campaign pay back the rest of
the ad spend and we're good and so by
having cash flow I can test I can
experiment and I can reach our goals
the clients that we work with make
millions of dollars in their businesses
you know we work with clients that are
beginners as well that are starting from
zero and we have clients that we've
helped start from zero to make millions
of dollars in their businesses the
methods that we teach work they're not
on trial
but they focus on a revenue first
approach okay we care about impacting
people we care about delivering the
highest quality value and service the
reason why we can actually deliver the
highest quality value products and
services is because of the cash flow
that comes in the only reason why I'm
able to make a free podcast like this
every single week and provide value to
you is because
we bring in cash flow through the other
avenues in our business okay
and so you have to make the Supreme
priority in your business as a coach be
sales and marketing and bringing in
revenue and cash flow so that you can
then fund the dream of the stuff that
you want to do in your business
if you're not focused on that you're
going to get way too caught up in the
weeds of doing everything perfect
because you're not trying to bring in
the revenue and unfortunately there's
all these quote graphics and things out
there like you know don't focus on the
money just focus on the process things
like that again I believe in that I
believe in the money Will Follow by
focusing on the process but you can't
make the money be a non-issue
you have to be able to pay the bills pay
the ad spend you have to think of it as
a business owner a business owner has a
responsibility to be prudent with their
finances and to increase the amount of
finances that come in
and so for you to be able to reach your
goals as a business owner you need to
think like a business owner
which is where cash flow is King
not just cash is King but cash flow
having a flow of cash come in that if
you have a losing month it replaces
itself next month without you having to
work hard to do that and this is the
mindset that I want you to get into is
one of an entrepreneur a capitalist
entrepreneur
that makes as much money as possible
as much as humanly possible
and does so for the purpose of
impacting people
for the purpose of reaching more people
with your message so that you can
increase the cash flow
and it becomes this wheel that feeds
itself and when you do it right you
don't have to wonder or struggle is it
going to work is it going to produce the
amount of money that we need to make are
these campaigns going to produce a
result you know I'm excited in the next
couple of weeks we're going to be
testing out some new campaigns I'm
really excited honestly like I'm I'm
almost like vibrating so much with
excitement around what we're going to be
doing because I know what's going to
come out of it I know what happened the
last six months when we've done this
we've been in in in a test phase in our
business for the last six months in the
last seven months we brought in
over 600 000 in sales in our business
just by testing
and so now my goal is how can I 10x that
to 6 million dollars in our business
in a year or two from now and then 60
million dollars in our business and see
that's where I'm dreaming of
I'm thinking about 60 million 100
million dollar levels
you know those of you that might know my
mom Sandy Krakowski she's been in
business for 30 years
and you know in the last year she just
increased her net worth by over 10
million dollars in just the last year
and I've seen how she's done it and I'm
like if my mom can do it I can as well
and if my mom can do it you can as well
you want to know what that's how you
impact people's lives that's how you set
free you know victims of child
trafficking that's how you make a change
in the world
is by having cash flow is by having
income entrepreneurs change and shape
the world we're looking at the world
around us right now the world is being
shaped by entrepreneurs that decided to
take risks
and I believe that the coaching industry
the mentoring industry creating online
courses creating online trainings is the
best vehicle to generate startup capital
for you as a business owner for the
purpose of then rolling into passive
Investments what I would love to see you
do is start to bring in one to five
million dollars a year by the way about
three to five million is the easiest to
maintain with the lowest amount of
effort
once you hit about three to five million
a year
it'll actually run itself and you only
have to show up about five to ten hours
a week below three million dollars a
year you got to work harder above 5
million a year it also takes harder but
it's like The Sweet Spot about three to
five million a year you can basically
retire
from the coaching business it's really
pretty cool I saw like three other
coaches post this the other week and I
was like that's absolutely correct and
all the businesses that we built we
found were right around that three to
five million dollar year mark it's the
perfect sustainable level and then when
you pour that money into passive
Investments it's able to then pay you
dividends and increase your net worth
through real estate through stocks
through investing through commercial
property
through venture capital
through private Equity okay
and so think bigger have a bigger
picture have a bigger vision for where
you're going in your life have a bigger
vision for the future see
in the last 200 episodes of this podcast
we've really ebbed and flowed with a lot
of where beginners are at and I'm about
to take it to the next level with you
for me to go to the next level I'm about
to take y'all to the next level
and what that means is you need to have
a vision that's bigger than just where
you're at right now and even if you're
just starting out at zero
have a vision for at least a couple
hundred thousand dollars a year minimum
you know that's that's just a baseline
middle class income right now in this
economy in 2023. you might say no it's
not absolutely it is look at the numbers
economically of Baseline middle class
income
accounted for by inflation
and a quarter of a million dollars is
actually considered middle class an
average home for a family of three to
four people it costs a half a million
dollars now doesn't cost a core of a
million everything's double what it was
two years ago three years ago the
economy has shifted after covid the
whole world has shifted and now the
world is being driven by ai ai first is
the way that a lot of companies are
thinking
and so we have to innovate and we have
to learn how can we bring in as much
cash flow as possible
to have the kind of impact that we want
to have if you want to impact the world
around you
you have to have cash flow to do so okay
and so I just I just want to encourage
you and challenge you
that if you just want to have impact if
you just want to make a little bit of
money shift your thinking grow your
thinking to be above just your current
present situation and realize that
making
more money than just what you need to
pay your bills
making above and beyond just the basics
it what you what do you do with that
extra money you invest it into you can
hire people to do the work for you so
now you can remove yourself from the
business you can pay for better systems
you can pay for advertising
and you can do so without stress you can
enjoy a more stress-free life you hire
out things in your household you hire
out things in your daily life
okay
no again I have these people they write
me they come to me I had somebody write
me the other day that's like can you
just stop talking about making so much
money
and just tell me how to teach people
better
and I'm like no that's that's that's not
that's not me I'm the money guy I'm the
I'm the guy that shows you how to get
super rich as a coach Mentor speaker
and and I'm leaning into that more and
more that I'm the money guy that I'm the
guy that you go to
for financial increase in your coaching
business
I'm not the one that you go to about you
know how do you be the world's best
coach best trainer and while I can show
you how to do that I've actually really
learned well how to coach how to teach
how to Mentor how to speak well I was a
terrible public speaker a couple years
ago
this podcast has helped me do that the
content on my social media how did I get
better at it by actually just doing the
work by being consistent
by staying and sticking with the process
and then what we found is what's the
lane of people that we best impact it's
the coaches mentors and speakers and
trainers that want to make a quarter of
a million to a half a million dollars a
year
to how do you get you to that level what
is that that's just a twenty to forty
thousand dollar a month income
very sustainable very doable my wife and
I haven't earned less than that in years
and I can show you how to do that in our
coaching programs with this podcast with
our virtual events that we put on
but if you're someone who's listening to
this right now you're like I just don't
want to make a lot of money I just I
just I just wanna
I just want to teach my sessions I just
want to train people
great teach train
do that that's fine I wanna I wanna have
acceptance for that
but I want to say that if you're in my
space
some of this economic capitalism is
going to rub off on you
and I think it should and I think it's a
good thing and I think more of us need
to start thinking
from a perspective of how can we make
more Revenue
and how can we use that money to impact
more people
I think that by doing so
the whole world's going to get a whole
lot better
my goal and my mission is to create a
thousand millionaire coaches not a
thousand coaches that have a bunch of
great ideas and courses and don't make
any money a thousand millionaire coaches
that's going to start by creating over a
thousand six-figure earning coaches you
know I told this person who was tired of
me talking about this the lady was like
if I join your coaching program will you
stop talking about money and I'm like no
uh you probably shouldn't join my
coaching program then that's such a
problem
it was such a stark example of like who
I don't want in my coaching program and
who is not a good fit that it like it
really stuck with me and it actually
inspired this podcast episode you'd be
surprised some of my episodes are
inspired by just silly stuff that people
say
so
if you're a coach if you're a mentor if
you're a trainer if you're a speaker
start to expand your mind about making
more money
make it important for you
stop thinking tiny stop thinking small
stop thinking about little itty bitty
bitty amounts
it's possible for you if it's possible
for my mom to go for me and a single mom
living on five thousand dollars a year
in a one-bedroom apartment with me when
she was Raising Me
to be in a multi-millionaire
female business owner
entrepreneur building an empire changing
her family line impacting millions of
lives around the world by the way
it's not just about the money it is
about the impact
but money is a is a massive part every
decision my mom makes in business starts
with is this going to be profitable for
us that's it every decision that a good
business owner makes starts with that
question is this going to be profitable
for us
when you start thinking in that
perspective of profit first
your impact will actually greatly
increase you will be able to impact more
people by being focused on making a
massive amount of profit in your
business
all right and so listen this podcast is
called grow your life
we might be renaming the podcast soon
about being a wealthy coach
a wealthy Mentor a wealthy speaker
you know speakers mentors and coaches
are kind of our our lane of people that
we help
and we help them get really stinking
wealthy doing so and so but for the time
being again grow your life it's about
expanding your reach it's about
expanding
what you can do what you can accomplish
and cash flow is a big part of that all
right listen share this with somebody
might be struggling with their thoughts
about making money maybe they're a
mentor maybe they're a speaker maybe
they're they're wondering you know
what's the best path of growth it's
always cash flow it's always revenue
revenue always solves every single
problem in your business because it
allows you to to actually hire out the
problem solvers I would rather hire
somebody to solve my problem
then try to solve it myself
and when you start thinking in that
direction and we stop making it All
About Us and how can I prove that I'm
smart and not going to make people like
me now can I make people approve of me
and we just go out there we think of it
from the standpoint of how can I bring
in the most amount of profit in my
business
and impact people simultaneously you'll
you'll be surprised how how well things
actually do for you and when you follow
the system that I teach because I teach
a whole system
that works I teach a system for coaches
and mentors that brings in massive
amounts of cash flow for them
when you apply that and you actually do
the work instead of getting stuck in
your head
thinking about procrastinating
overthinking which all that's natural
and normal a lot of people do that I
struggle with that for years it's you
know so don't beat yourself up over that
it's a normal thing to do but
when you shift into how can I start to
take as much action as possible and how
can I start to move the needle forward
towards my goals you will be shocked
how well stuff works out for you by
taking risk by making it an experiment
by being willing to
put yourself out there
no matter who judges you no matter who
thinks
whatever they want to think about you
and you just show up consistently
the cash flow starts to follow and the
impact grows exponentially I'll tell you
as my income has grown my impact has
grown my impact was stagnated when my
income was also stagnated
so keep that in mind in every business
that I've grown I've seen people impact
millions of lives
and cash flow directly correlates to
that
and it will for you as well grow your
life everybody and we'll talk soon have
a good one
foreign
[Music]